fuccha.in 2019-06-11

# FUCCHA- Voice of YOUth! | Fastest Growing YOUth Media Platform in India

### FUCCHA (n)

A Fearless Youngster willing to  
Explore Things

## Privacy Policy

### Introduction

  * The protection of privacy and security of your personal information is important to FUCCHA.IN (“Company”), a company incorporated under the laws of India. We therefore conduct our business, and collect information in compliance with the applicable laws in India and keeping with the following security practices. Our Privacy Policy;?%3Epage/privacy_policy) discloses our information practices regarding information being collected, method of such information collection, use of such information, information sharing if any with third parties, measures to safeguard information collected and the choices that you make about the way such information is collected, used and disclosed including accessing and updating the information. 
  * By using/accessing/registering on www.FUCCHA.IN (“Site”) you agree to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy;?%3Epage/privacy_policy). This Privacy Policy;?%3Epage/privacy_policy) applies regardless of the means or device you use to access the Site. It is clarified that the Company has adopted these privacy principles for the Site alone. This Privacy Policy;?%3Epage/privacy_policy) does not apply to any other third party or to any third party sites which can be accessed using the links available on the Site. Personal Information shall, for this Privacy Policy;?%3Epage/privacy_policy), include without limitation, any information that identifies, or can be used to identify, contact or locate you, including, but not limited to, name, photograph, salutation, gender, address, phone number and email address, etc.(“Personal Information”). Terms capitalised but not defined herein shall have the same meaning ascribed to them in the Terms of Use. 

### PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT

  * We only collect Personal Information that you choose to provide us or for the collection of which we have your consent under this Privacy Policy;?%3Epage/privacy_policy). Through your use of this Site, we will not collect any Personal Information about you unless you voluntarily choose to provide us with the same. However, for safety and security reasons we will monitor your usage of the Site through cookies as mentioned in our Terms of Use.
  * We collect Personal Information in the following ways: 
    * When you register online for accessing, submitting or enteringany information/content/inputs being offered on the Site;
    * When you upload, transmit, display, perform or distribute Content and other Personal Information;
    * When you participate in any contests, sweepstakes and/or promotions;
    * When you post on a message board;
    * When you participate in any survey or poll conducted on the Site, either by the Company or through third parties;
    * When you send SMS, MMS or other mobile device based messages;
    * When you interact with the content available on the Site;
    * When you sign up to receive emails or other communications from the Company or other third parties through the Site;
    * When you contact us with a question or comment;
    * When you expressly enter information into a text field, post any content or otherwise submit information to us.
  * We will only collect Personal Information as is permitted by applicable laws and regulations in India. You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information notwithstanding any other law applicable to you, however, not providing this information may prevent you from accessing the information available on the Site. 

### COLLECTION OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

  * We may automatically collect certain information from your visit to the Site such as your information about the domain name of the website from which you came, information relating to frequency of visits, average time spent, pages viewed during the visit, your IP address, name of your internet service provider, device specific information, your browser type, operating system and language, your device etc. (“Non-Personal Information”).This Non-Personal Information is anonymous information that cannot be easily used to personally identify you. We may use such Non-Personal Information for the purposes of administering the Site, analysing user trends, gathering demographic information, ascertaining how our visitors use our Site, evaluating your use of the information on the Site and to improve content on our Site and performance. 
  * We may share this Non-Personal Information with third party service providers and advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, if any, content programming and for other bonafide purposes as we may desire, at our sole discretion. By using our Site you expressly provide us with your consent to access such information for one or more purposes deemed fit by the Company. 

### USING THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

  * You explicitly consent to the Site and the Company using your Personal Information by (i) using this Site, (ii) registering with this Site, (iii) providing Personal Information or (iv) opting in when presented with the choice, you explicitly consent to the Company using your Personal Information, subject to applicable laws.
  * We will use the Personal Information provided by you, more elaborately, to: 
    * Facilitate in providing the services and features that most likely meet your needs;
    * Facilitate in providing the information/content/inputs as submitted/posted by you for brand campaigns to users; 
    * Facilitate in providing the information you request (e.g. send you by email or other electronic means the information); Manage our relationship with you; 
    * Inform you of products, promotions and competitions which you may find interesting; 
    * Respond to any queries you may have;
    * Monitor and improve our Site;
    * Develop a more direct relationship with you for the purposes described in this section; 
    * Deliver content and information via SMS, MMS and other mobile services; 
    * To enhance and support our relationship with you including to inform you if we change anything important about how the Site works;
  * The Site will collect, use or disclose the Personal Information provided by you and/or collected by us as mentioned in this Privacy Policy;?%3Epage/privacy_policy) only for the purposes disclosed to you, unless the disclosure: 
    * is a use of the Personal Information for any additional purpose that is directly related to the original purpose for which the Personal Information was collected,
    * is necessary to prepare, negotiate and perform a contract with you,
    * is required by law or the competent governmental or judicial authorities,
    * is necessary to establish or preserve a legal claim or defence,
    * is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activities, such as wilful attacks on our information technology systems.
  * Please note that we cannot and will not be responsible for other parties' use of the Personal Information which you make available for public view through the Site.

### MARKETING PURPOSES

  * By accessing the Site, you provide us with your consent to use your Personal Information for marketing purposes.
  * It is clarified that your participation in marketing activities is voluntary and if you ever want to change your preferences regarding the use of your Personal Information and would like us to remove your information from our marketing e-mails or newsletters, unsubscribe you from our database, or if you info@fuccha.in . Please include your name, email address, and clear instructions regarding any changes you are requesting.

### COOKIES

  * When you access the Site, we send standard technology called “cookies” and web server logs to your computer, to collect information about how the Site is used, for record-keeping purposes and to help automatically recognize your computer the next time you access the Site. The cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. The Company may use Cookies, and other methods, to store and retrieve data from your web browser. Cookies help us tailor the services offered by the Site to suit your needs and to enhance your online experience and to improve the design and content of the Site to suit your needs. We use this information to do internal research on our user’s demographics, interests, and behaviour to understand, protect and serve our users. Additionally, you may encounter ‘cookies’ or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. 
  * If you do not wish to receive cookies, please configure your Internet browser to erase all cookies from your computer's hard drive, block all cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, blocking Company cookies may disable certain features on our Site and may make it impossible for you to use certain services available on our Site. This may also affect your overall content experience with us. 

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

You have successfully reviewed this college!

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

We sent otp to your mobile number. Please check and enter OTP.

### Join Now- It's FREE and

#### always will be 

I accept [ T&C](http://www.fuccha.in/terms-conditions) and allow FUCCHA Media to contact me

If you sign up with Facebook or Google, we’ll automatically import your bio which you will be able to edit/change after logging in. We’ll never post to Facebook without your permission. We take privacy very seriously. For more info, please see our [T&C](http://www.fuccha.in/terms-conditions)

If you sign up with Facebook or Google, we’ll automatically import your bio which you will be able to edit/change after logging in. We’ll never post to Facebook without your permission. We take privacy very seriously. For more info, please see our [T&C](http://www.fuccha.in/terms-conditions)
